(Sheldon:)This is ridiculous.
We're shopping for a party.
This store doesn't have a party section.
(Penny:)Yeah, it does, and here we are.
(Sheldon:)I have to say, Penny,
I don't understand why you, of all people...
(Sheldon:)...are encouraging Leonard to do this.
(Penny:)Well, I'm his girlfriend,
of course I'm gonna support him.
(Sheldon:)Well, you're his girlfriend for now.
(Sheldon:)Maybe you're not aware of this,
but there is a rich tradition of men at sea...
(Sheldon:)...finding comfort in each other's arms
and britches.
(Penny:)Honey, this is a big deal for Leonard, okay?
(Penny:)He gets to work with Stephen Hawking, who,
by the way, will not be on the boat, I checked.
It's not that big of an opportunity. I mean,
even if Hawking's theories are correct...
(Sheldon:)...all they prove is
where the universe came from...
(Sheldon:)...why everything exists
and what its ultimate end will be.
(Sheldon:)Me? I'm interested in the big questions.